[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Security professionals are tasked with the protection of persons, property, and",
		"correct": "Information",
		"options": [
			"Government buildings",
			"Employee belongings",
			"Information",
			"Military locations"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "Individuals holding an individual security licence in the province of Alberta may not refer to themselves as:",
		"correct": "Peace officers",
		"options": [
			"Security professionals",
			"Loss prevention workers",
			"Peace officers",
			"Watchpersons"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": " Professionalism is best demonstrated by:",
		"correct": "Peace officers",
		"options": [
			"Your conduct and deportment",
			"Loss prevention workers",
			"Peace officers",
			"Watchpersons"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "Your conduct and deportment __________________ utilized by licensed security professionals must be authorized by the Registrar",
		"correct": "Batons",
		"options": ["Batons", "Reporting forms", "Post orders", "Safety equipment"]
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "The notes in your notebook will help you:",
		"correct": "Prepare reports for your employer and others",
		"options": [
			"Prepare reports for your employer and others",
			"Avoid court testimony",
			"Obtain a security licence in another    classification",
			"Communicate non-verbally "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "Writing profanity in your notebook is:",
		"correct": "Acceptable when you are quoting verbatim",
		"options": [
			"Never appropriate",
			"Acceptable when you are quoting verbatim",
			"Inadmissible in court",
			"Prohibited under the Security Services and Investigator’s Act"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "A statement is usually gathered as part of the _____________ process.",
		"correct": "Interview",
		"options": [
			"Use of force",
			"Interview",
			"Verbal communication",
			"Post-order"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "When you lose your security licence, you must file a written report to:",
		"correct": "The Registrar of Security programs",
		"options": [
			"The police",
			"The Registrar of Security programs",
			"Your supervisor",
			"The client where you lost your licence"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "A security professional in the province of Alberta must be, at minimum, _________years of age.",
		"correct": "18",
		"options": ["16", "18", "19", "21"]
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "A licensed security professional may perform the following tasks:",
		"correct": "All of the above",
		"options": [
			"Monitoring of alarm systems",
			"Arrest of persons found committing a crime",
			"Responding to emergencies",
			"Conducting physical searches of purses,   backpacks, and other personal items",
			"All of the above"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "Protecting information may include limiting access of persons to computer equipment and data.",
		"correct": "True",
		"options": ["True", "False"]
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "An individual holding a security licence is licensed to work as a private detective when:",
		"correct": "Never",
		"options": [
			"Directed by the licensee’s employer",
			"The security professional is directed to  protect information",
			"The work of another employee must be covered due to illness or vacation",
			"Never"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 13,
		"question": "Uniform requirements for licensed security professionals are designated by:",
		"correct": "The Security Services and Investigators Act",
		"options": [
			"The Employment Standards Code and  Regulation",
			"The Security Operations Standards Council",
			"The Security Services and Investigators Act",
			"The Alberta Association of Chiefs of Police"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 14,
		"question": "The main duties of a security professional are to:",
		"correct": "Observe, deter, report",
		"options": [
			"Observe, notify, arrest ",
			"Observe, deter, report",
			"c.	Concentrate, notice, recall ",
			"d.	Contain, deter, arrest "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 15,
		"question": "When approached by media, you should: ",
		"correct": "Observe, deter, report",
		"options": [
			"a.	Tell them “no comment”",
			"b.	Ignore them",
			"c.	Only provide “yes” or “no” answers ",
			"d.	Refrain from participating in an interview"
		]
	}
]
